http://www.geo-tools.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

www.Geo-Tools.com
Welcome to Geo-Tools.com, your one stop shop for all your Geological, Mineral, and Fossil tool and equipment needs!
How To Contact Us
Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Geological Tools and Outfitter, LLC website, www.geo-tools.com . On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, Credit/Debit Card Information.How We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. If you contact us we reserve the right to provide you information concerning product sales or other promotions. You may respond to these emails and request to be removed from our mailing list. If you choose not to purchase items on our site you can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by personally contacting me at glade@geo-tools.com. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
If there are any other considerations or circumstances about your order that have not been discussed here, contact Geological Tools and Outfitter, LLC web sales staff at orders@geo-tools.com or call 435-225-8665.
About Us
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Site Map
Search Terms
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
Contact Us
© 2015 Geological Tools and Outfitter, LLC. All Rights Reserved. | Web Design by Pixel It Perfect
